You are going to listen to some different guys that talk too much coffee from Costa Rica and describe to you like sugarcane, tapadulce, molasses, cacao, golden berry, and we want that you are going to taste and you are going to understand some different flavors.
Yes, tell me, do any or all of these grow near or close to the coffees?
Yes.
Well, I don't have a farm, but I live in a coffee growing region in the mountains of the Central Valley, and this is the rose apple.
And this is you can see in the borders of the roads.
This is used to be more common to find in the city or in the backyards, but like a disease or organism just kind of like cut down these trees.
So now it's kind of a little bit rare to find.
You are lucky, man.
Yeah.
Rose apple.
It smells like an apple.
It tastes like an apple.
It's more floral than an apple.
Okay.
Another is like tapadulce or sugarcane juice.
It's a very typical, how can I say that, typical flavor in my coffee.
This is the fruit platter after the third round.
Everybody has a fruit on their table.
The next one is a farmer with four bags.
Ha ha ha ha.
The good man is licking the fruit.
These judges are very cute.
Ha ha ha ha.